34-menopause-symptoms.com 2019-01-17

# 34-Menopause-Symptoms.com Privacy Policy | 34 Menopause Symptoms

This Privacy Policy discloses 34-Menopause-Symptoms.com information gathering and use practices for personal information of each visitor to and user of ("you" or a "user") its website https://www.34-menopause-symptoms.com (the "site").

## The Information 34-Menopause-Symptoms.com Collects

User-provided information: 34-Menopause-Symptoms.com receives and stores any information you enter on our site, or provide to 34-Menopause-Symptoms.com in any other way, such as e-mail communication through the site.

  *  **Cookie Information.** When you visit the site, 34-Menopause-Symptoms.com may send one or more cookies-a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters-to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the site may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.
  *  **Log file information.** When you use the site, 34-Menopause-Symptoms.com servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

## The Way 34-Menopause-Symptoms.com Uses Information

34-Menopause-Symptoms.com may use your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information to contact you regarding your interest in 34-Menopause-Symptoms.com's available products and to communicate with you regarding any requested information as disclosed on the form or registration. You will have the ability to opt out of such contacts. 34-Menopause-Symptoms.com may also use your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of Site changes or for customer service purposes). 34-Menopause-Symptoms.com will treat such personally identifiable information as confidential while it is in 34-Menopause-Symptoms.com's possession. However, standard e-mail and online forms are not secure and it is possible that your information can be viewed or retrieved by others when transmitted via the Internet without 34-Menopause-Symptoms.com 's knowledge or authorization.

34-Menopause-Symptoms.com uses both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as the log file data) to improve the quality and design of the Site and for other system administration purposes. 34-Menopause-Symptoms.com does not link log file information or IP addresses to personally identifiable information.

## When 34-Menopause-Symptoms.com Discloses Information

34-Menopause-Symptoms.com may provide personally identifiable information and non-personally-identifiable information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, and contractors for the purpose of providing and maintaining our services or fulfilling your request or registration. 34-Menopause-Symptoms.com requires that these parties agree to use such information solely for this purpose, and uses reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information and to use other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

34-Menopause-Symptoms.com may release personally identifiable information or non-personally-identifiable information:

  * If required to do so by law
  * In the good-faith belief that release or disclosure of such information action is necessary to comply with state, federal, and international laws or respond to a court order, subpoena, or search warrant
  * To enforce this Privacy Policy or other legal or proprietary rights of 34-Menopause-Symptoms.com
  * In the good-faith belief that release or disclosure is necessary to protect the safety, rights, or property of 34-Menopause-Symptoms.com, its employees, or others.

## Links to Other Sites

34-Menopause-Symptoms.com is not responsible for the privacy policies of any sites that are linked to the site. You should consult the respective privacy policies associated with these sites for more information on their practices. 34-Menopause-Symptoms.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and 34-Menopause-Symptoms.com cannot control the activities of, such other websites.

## International Users

If you are a user accessing the site from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the Site, which is governed by U.S. law and this privacy policy, you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer.

## In the Event of Merger or Sale

In the event that all or part of 34-Menopause-Symptoms.com is acquired by or merged with a third-party entity, you agree that 34-Menopause-Symptoms.com may transfer or assign the information collected from our Users as part of such merger, acquisition, or other change of control.

## Changes and Updates to this Privacy Policy

This privacy policy may be revised periodically, as reflected by the update date below. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. In general, 34-Menopause-Symptoms.com will use your personal information only in the manner described in the privacy policy in effect when 34-Menopause-Symptoms.com received the personal information you provided. Your continued use of the site constitutes your agreement to this privacy policy and any future revisions.

Last Update: AUGUST-11-2016

## Updating, Changing, or Deleting Your Information

If you want to update or delete your personal information from 34-Menopause-Symptoms.com's systems, please request it through our contact form. There may be some lag time between the moment you contact us and the moment the update or deletion takes place in our systems.

## Contact Information

Please contact 34-Menopause-Symptoms.com through the following [contact form](https://www.34-menopause-symptoms.com/contact-us.htm) with any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy.
